"G" is for the Green Witch
Withering in the hot sunlight
"W" is for the Water Witch
Boiled away by fire torture
"S" is for the Stone Witch
Hammered into little pieces
"E" is for the Eastern Witch
Who fell into a pit so bye-bye
"B" is for the Beast Witch
Who was terrified one day by a sharp spear
"C" is for the Champignon Witch
Poison doesn't bother her
She's the really scary one
'Cause she's gonna bring
The End of All Things
There are lots of devils.
Drive them all away!
Yes! I win!
EPISODE 9: THE HOUSE IN THE BLACK FOREST
Kids from the village. The
adults tell them to stay away
but sometimes they come to play
this close to the forest anyway.
Lize, let's get going.
End of All Things?
Don't let that stuff get to you.
I was told I need to find great happiness,
but sometimes I'm consumed
by such an intense sadness,
I can't put it down in my diary.
How would you handle something
like that, Miss Witch?
I know it sounded immature and corny,
but I worked up the courage to ask anyway.
I try to remember something sad that
I keep locked up inside, cry over it,
and use those tears as a bed
to grow more mushrooms.
Then I make tea with those tear mushrooms,
drink it, and cry more to detox.
It really helps me calm down.
Then I use the tears I cried
to make more mushrooms.
She responded with an off-kilter
but very practical answer.
Don't worry. It's caffeine-free.
That's not really the issue.
Would you like to watch me make the tea?
I don't know why she
suddenly seemed so eager,
but I got the strong impression
that I shouldn't say no.
Wow! It smells nice!
But I've never smelled anything
like it. A very unique smell.
It was lush but delicate, and made me
imagine floating in a warm ocean.
A very mellow fragrance.
Um...
I did extract all of the poison,
but don't force yourself
if you think it's gross.
As Miss Witch nervously stammered her
insistence she'd removed all the poison,
I thought she looked kind of cute.
But, wait.
The tears these mushrooms grew from,
they were part of Miss Witch's body...
Why's he suddenly look so intense?
You'd better not be thinking
something dirty, kid.
Back off, crow.
Wow! This smells delicious! Thank you!
Ah...
Oh!
I had so many tears.
There was enough sadness and pain
inside me to fill up a whole cup.
I didn't lose the memories
the sadness had been linked to,
and the mushrooms that came from my tears
looked like emerald mixed into a sky blue.
They had a deep, very lovely color.
Miss Witch took them, sliced them,
dried them,
fried them to remove the poison,
and boiled out the memories.
By the time the tea from
my tear mushrooms was ready,
my heart felt almost as unbelievably
sunny and clear as the blue sky.
It's up to you to decide
when you should drink it.
Don't forget to collect the tears
you cry in a cup, though.
It was a very well-polished tear ceremony.
There were jars of Miss Witch's tear tea.
It must have taken many nights of feeling
very sad to have made so much tea.
I wonder just how many nights
Miss Witch had felt like that.
I wonder how many days
she's spent like this,
quietly enduring the
embrace of such sadness.
I also made some tea
to help you sleep, Claude.
Lize.
I would start to wonder about that
during our tear mushroom tea parties
so they always left me
feeling a little melancholy.
Ooh!
Uh-oh, Luna. Did you accidentally
give the crow tear tea, too?
If he realizes, he'll kill me!
I didn't see a thing.
Gosh, I didn't know the crow
had any tears inside him.
Gross.
Caw.
Caw!
Miss Witch, I have a question.
Good. He's getting serious about studying.
What is going on here? What
are these two people doing?
I take it back.
It says something about a "kiss,"
but why would these people
be doing something like this?
Is this brat for real?
Um, are you all right, Miss Witch?
Don't let him get to you, Luna!
W-Well...
Would he really lose his memories
about something like that?
A kiss is something people
do when they're very close.
A sign of intimacy,
kind of like a greeting.
Have you ever kissed someone
before, Miss Witch?
Man, he's aggressive!
She froze.
She's not moving.
She's malfunctioning.
Exactly how close do people
have to be in order to kiss?
Does our relationship count as
being that close, Miss Witch?
This little shit!
He shall cloak himself in
a semblance of innocence...
Or does the relationship
between you and I
not really count as that close?
At that moment, the crow thought,
"I'll be damned. I guess that's
one way to try to steal a kiss."
Excerpted from the memoirs
of Claude the crow.
Th-That definition of a kiss
applies to normal people.
It doesn't apply to someone
with a poison body like me.
That's a pretty decent comeback for Luna.
Um, I think...
that even if we have to do
it through a magic cloth,
I would like to kiss you, Miss Witch.
Huh?!
This brat never gives up!
Even strangers kiss each other's hands.
I heard that's just being polite.
Give it a rest, you little shit!
I hope that someday you let me
place one on your lips, Miss Witch.
Okay, I'm going to go practice my magic!
Luna?
That brat. He knew exactly how to give
a formal kiss on the hand, didn't he?
The nerve of that little white witch punk!
You don't know what a kiss is, huh?!
That whole damn thing was an act!
Miss Witch was so pretty!
Today I feel like I'll be able to do the
hard magic I struggled with in training!
It feels like my heart's sprouted wings.
It feels like I can do anything!
Shopping in the village?
You really want me to go?
Yeah, you'll be doing us a favor,
and it'll also give us a way to evaluate
your magic progress. A preliminary test.
And he'll keep an eye on you.
Me?
Luna is always protecting you
so maybe you didn't realize,
but a kid like you who can't
really handle his magic yet
is an easy target for all sorts
of demons and poison creatures.
I'm sure you'll see some
once you're out of the forest
and outside of Luna's protection.
Demons and poison creatures?
Use the magic you've learned so far
to protect yourself and the bull
and complete the job.
If you can't pull that much off, well,
you'd be abandoned anyway.
Or if you're chicken and
would rather be babysat here
while you play house in your wee
little garden, then suit yourself.
But I'll tell you one thing. You sure
as hell better not try to run away.
If you do run, I'll turn
that guy into stew.
Crows sure do love their stew!
"Babysat" by Luna and "playing house"...
I'll go. I won't try to run away.
I will complete the job safely
and return to this house!
"BEEF STEW"
So he's basically just running errands.
Y-Yeah.
You've got nothing to worry
about with me by your side.
Once we clear those two hills,
we'll be in Musher Village.
Okay.
But you know, if I did
get turned into stew,
it'd probably be the most delicious stew
in the world. Don't you think so, Lize?
Huh? Well...
But I still don't want to get eaten,
so you better not run away.
Minos, we'll have time to eat
lunch later. Let's keep walking.
I want some of that grass over there, too!
Minos, come on!
Looks like tonight's dinner will
be rotten beef stew after all.
"Minos! Return!"
Lize, let's hurry to the village.
I can smell some really tasty
grass along the road ahead.
What the hell did he just do?
Did he use spirit language for a second?
Lize, I offer you the
blessing of the trees.
Thank you!
Oh, it's a snail.
It's a poison creature, so be careful.
Don't get too close, Lize.
Poison creatures?
What are those?
Living creatures that have ingested
too much of the world's poisons
and were completely poisoned...
and transformed.
Some of them are turned into one
by other poison creatures.
Those fellows aren't demons, though.
But you've got to learn the difference.
Be careful, Lize.
I don't think this guy
is gonna do anything.
Just don't step in his
poisonous slime, okay?
He must be in a lot of pain.
If Luna was here, she could
have absorbed his poison
and made him a little more
comfortable, at least.
When Miss Witch encounters poison
creatures, does she absorb their poison?
Only enough to give them a little relief.
She used to sprinkle
poison-sucking spores on them,
but that made the mushrooms grow too big,
even though it did take away the pain.
So now she puts a sheet on
them that absorbs the poison
and keeps the miasma
from spreading around.
Oh, look. Those guys are wearing
sheets that Luna gave them.
Huh? What now? You have a friend
back there who wants a sheet, too?
Hmm. Well, that's too bad.
Sorry guys, but Luna isn't here today.
She'll come by again, though.
How do the sheets fit?
Miss Witch...
Just right? Good! I'm glad to hear it.
I'll tell Luna you said so.
I'm sure it will make her happy.
Miss Witch really is a wonderful person.
Well, of course she is.
All of us are just crazy about her.
Luna's an incredible witch.
Yeah, I think I'm crazy about her, too.
Someday, I want to become
a wonderful magician just like her.
Yeah, and I'm sure you will.
It makes me really happy
that you like Luna too, Lize.
I want to support her. I want to give
her strength and bring her happiness.
I want to be at least a small
source of joy in her life.
Let's hurry and get the goats
so we can go home, okay?
I'll go wherever I have to
in order to be there for her!
Look, Lize. There's the village!
We finished our shopping
in no time. Nice job, Lize!
Everyone was so friendly with you.
They did seem a little nervous, though.
I've never had such an easy time
shopping before. What a difference!
Now we just have to get home.
It's raining.
Lize, the rain's poisonous,
so remember what Luna told you.
Pull up your hood, cover your skin,
and don't forget your gloves.
Also, put the magic sheets
we brought on the goats.
What about you, Minos?
Oh, I'll be all right.
Huh?
Hurry up.
That's a poison creature!
What should we do, Lize?
Lize, I shall give you
three wishing seeds.
If there's a power you want to use
or a desire you wish fulfilled,
eat one of these and concentrate.
It will amplify your magic,
and grant any wish within our power.
Now, recite your true name.
Oh!
What is this power?
Lize, I think he's in pain.
The goat is in danger, too!
Please, loosen it and let them down.
I don't like this.
I really don't like this!
A huge flower?
The goat got scratched by the poison
claws but it's still alive, Lize.
That was wild, Lize! When did
you learn that kind of magic?
What are you doing, Lize?
Why did you waste wishing seeds
to save a creature like that?
Poison monsters like that harm us.
We hoped you'd eliminate it.
Are you in pain from the poison?
Were you after the magical
sheet the goat was wearing?
We don't have enough
fabric to give him one.
We need the goat's sheet
to bandage its wounds.
Lize, what are you doing?
Oh!
You used conjuring magic? You even
conjured one of Luna's magic sheets?
That's amazing, Lize!
You've gotten so much better!
Well, actually...
Oh, good. It fits perfectly.
That sheet is yours now.
What are you thinking, Lize?
How could you use the power we lent
you to help such an abomination?
I'm disappointed in you!
I don't wanna talk to you.
Think about what you did.
I'm going to learn magic on my own.
Thank you for the powers
you gave me until now.
But you're okay. Don't worry about it.
Just stop trying to
steal sheets from others,
and hurry on home.
I'm heading home now, too.
Lize, are you okay?
Minos, can you carry this goat?
We need Miss Witch to treat
the poison wounds immediately.
We have to hurry.
Lize, can you walk?
Do you want to ride, too?
No. I want to walk on my own two feet
to go back to Miss Witch.
I'm sure Miss Witch is
waiting for us right now.
Everyone in the black
forest is waiting for us.
And I'm anxious to return to that house.
I feel like I've finally found it...
a place that I can call home!
Luna, can you treat this goat's poison
with your mushrooms right away?
Mm-hmm.
See, aren't you glad I went with him?
Yeah, he would have been
in big trouble without me.
Mm-hmm.
TRANSLATION: MICHAEL ARNOLD
SUBTITLE TIMING: ANDY ELLIS
EDITING: ELISABETH CRIST
QUALITY CHECK: GABRIELLA ALABANZA
TRANSLATION CHECK: MICHELLE TYMON
NEXT TIME: REUNION